ED]
Ebikyuu!
Mayu!
I'm Sakurai-kun, attendance number 130,000, and I'm in fashion.
I'm Osawa and Ito, and this is Osawa and Taraka.
This is Arthur, the newest member of the Ebi team, who we haven't seen in a long time.
I'm sure it's been a while since we've seen each other, but how did you feel when you first met?
How did you feel when you met him for the first time in a long time?
His face has become smaller... but he seems to have lost some of his color.
The battle of the 500th anniversary of the Shrimp Festival
The first half of the battle is today!
We'll have the first half and the second half, but it's not easy to get everyone together, especially with the schedule and all.
How do you like it, Mr. Sakuragi? I've never done a comedy act before.
How long have you been practicing?
I've been watching you since you first gave me the job, and I check in with you between lessons, before and after the show.
We practiced a lot, checking things before and after the lesson.
When I first saw the script, I thought
What do you think?
I'm sure it's there, isn't it?
I don't know what to say.
What's the point?
What's so funny? I don't know.
Okay.
What do you mean?
You know, you've done that before.
We have that, too.
You're a veteran writer.
There are ways of doing things, but...
But when I saw it...
There are things from a generation I wasn't born into.
I wasn't born yet.
That's also difficult.
I'd like to ask you about that at the end of the story.
I'd like to hear about it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I think it's going to be a little rough today.
So, I'd like you to listen to the song here.
I'd like you to listen to a song here.
It's Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku.
How's today?
How are you doing today?
Now, the members of Ebichu are currently preparing their material, so it's just us old guys here.
There's a different kind of tension here.
That's right.
I guess it's this... thing... that's really on our minds.
That's right. That's why we're writing the script.
That's right.
That's why I think I'll talk more.
Right, before you see the story.
That's right.
They have a lot of insurance.
I'm sure each of you has plenty of excuses.
Yes, yes, yes, yes
Once again, I'd like to introduce you to this year's Neta Battle, in which the ten members of Ebichu will be divided into four teams to compete with each other in a story produced by four of us comedians.
We had a lottery to decide the teams before, and I, Ito team is the trio of Sakuragi, Cocona, Hoshinamire, and Yasumoto, Ayaka.
Eggplant team is a trio of Noka Kazami and Ema Sakurai Hatanaka team is a trio of Rika Mayama and Yamanashi Nakayama Nakanishi team is a trio of Kaho Kobayashi, Yuna Nakamura, and
Kokubou Yu's
I think we are a trio now.
So...
It's different again with a duo and a trio, and
Combi and trio.
The way we fight.
Well, the question is whether it's going to be a comic or a comedy.
I guess so.
We'll see how it goes.
So, the two Oswalds...
You both write the material?
Yes, that's right.
We come up with a theme, and then we make it up as we go along.
I see. I see. Because, Mr. Ito, you do pin stories, too, don't you?
Can you tell us a little about the titles of your pin stories?
Let's see, it's Chobi Hige Cat's Eye.
I also make pin stories.
If they write Chobi Hige Cat's Eye.
What is the Chobihige Cat's Eye that will appear this time?
Well, I'm sorry, I can't say anything about it.
I see. I can't say.
Is there a possibility that he might appear?
That would be a spoiler, wouldn't it?
If it becomes a spoiler, we'll have to probe each other.
Do you usually write stories?
I don't write anything at all.
You don't write?
You must have had a hard time making a story.
Well, I don't know.
So, I now understand how great you are, Mr. Nakanishi, who writes stories on a daily basis, more than ever.
No, no, no, but you cover for me in other ways, so that's totally fine.
No, no, no.No, no, no.
Pops, we're breaking up.
We're breaking up.
This is not the time.
It's not the time to be standing around in that convivia.
Is now a good time?
When you become an uncle, the corners are removed and you become rounded, and you get to know each other.
That's how it happens, gradually.
In the meantime, this week, the Ito team and the Nasu team will be performing their material.
I see.
I'm looking forward to it.
The Tsukkomi comedian team.
That's right.
And the judges will vote for the team that all of the Ebichu Minamitani Nen staff thought was the funniest.
After four weeks?
After two weeks, yes.
The team with the most votes will be the winner.
After the first half?
Yes, after the first and second rounds.
The Nas team and the Ito team are at a slight disadvantage in the first round, aren't they?
Freshness is very important in comedy.
They recently did "The Second," and I think the second half of the show has the advantage.
That's true.
They have a lot of insurance.
That's for sure.
You have insurance, don't you?
Who doesn't?
I've never written anything like that.
There's no such thing.
We're actually playing Ito's team.
Shall we decide on a penalty game?
Punishment?
Who gets punished?
Shouldn't we decide on the wording?
That's why we have to decide who will be punished.
Isn't that the leader?
What? The loser?
The one who made it?
The comedian of the losing team?
Or the performer who played Ebichu?
Or was it the staff who put the lowest team in?
Ahh...
That's a good one.
Or a staff pattern.
This one.
It's kind of weird to have zero responsibility, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
If you're on the staff and you don't have an eye for comedy...
If you're a staff member and you don't have an eye for comedy...
It's fatal.
Yes, that's true.
Because we are the only ones suffering.
That's right.
We've been very busy.
We're all over each other.
Erma's busy.
Even Ebitu is busy.
I mean, we've been working every day.
And I've never written a story.
That's a great point.
And the first subject is...
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
This is a bit...
So what should we do?
No questions asked, the staff will be punished.
Punishment?
No matter how it turns out.
Don't just sit around with your arms crossed.
That's right.
I'll ask the staff to copy and paste the story.
I'll ask the staff to do a quick copy.
I'll ask him to do it.
I see.
That's a good idea.
I'll get the bottom line.
I'll have them do the bottom line.
I'll have the staff member who placed the team in last place.
I'll have the person who put in the last-place team restore the last-place team's story.
May I?
I'm scared.
And so, as you can see...
It seems that the Ebichu members are ready to go, so
I'm ready.
Let's get right to the story.
First of all, who is it?
First of all
The top bill is the trio of Cocona Sakuragi, Nami Hoshi and Ayaka Yasumoto from Ito's team.
Are you ready? Let's start with the top story.
Here you go.
Choujo, Mirei
Jijo, CoconaJijo Coconer
Chairman Yasumoto
in conjunction with Mr.
Ebisu
Cat's Eye
There it is, there it is, the cat's eye.
Today, in order to win your heart
I'm going to do a short comedy for you.
We're going to show you what the three of us can do.
Okay, here we go.
I'll do the bank robbery.
I'll be the bank robber.
I'll do the bank robbery. You do the bank robbery.
No, I'll play the homeless girl.
Okay, you're in charge.
The Chairman of the Board will be the bank robber.
Yes, sir.
I'm out of time.
So you'll be the factory manager?
I'm counting on you.
Let's go.
It's a robbery. Give me the money.
If you feel sorry for me, give me the money.
Please. Please.
How the hell am I supposed to feed my mesh if they take this loan?
How the hell am I gonna feed the mesh?
No, a very popular bank.
It's not a very popular bank. Why do we have a bank robber, Yumi Adachi, and an old guy from the Sunday theater all in one place?
Why do you have a bank robber, Yumi Adachi, and an old guy from the Sunday theater all in one place?
If you want to excel, you'd better come up with a better plan.
It's long enough to break the false curtain.
It's not long, it's short.
Let's get back on track. Next is a short comedy, Lupin.
I'll do Lupin the Third and you do Captain Zenigata.
I'll do the voiceover.
I still love you. Then you play Inspector Sengata.
I'll do the skull eyes.
I'm counting on you! Let's go!
Lupin the Third... Lupin the Third...
Lupin the Third, you're punished... No, the same way...
Aaahhh!
Not the same way!
I've never seen Lupin III on location.
If you want to catch Lupin III too...
You should at least shut up and do Inspector Zenigata!
I don't want to end up like this.
I'd rather be Korogi no Funi than this
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
What's the matter with you two?
All I wanted was a short comedy
I'm the girl who flew with this guy...
I'm not giving up on you
There's a million guys out there.
I really liked her.
No, Hamaglia.
But that's enough! Catch! Thank you so much!
This is great! This is great!
I don't know how you remember all this.
That's great!
How did you learn it!
Not a single bite, not a single mistake.
That's great!
Now, let's hear from the top three who have done it!
Yes, sir!
How did you do, Mirei? What did you think?
I was so nervous!
I don't know...
Is this a comment?
It's a "tskkomi".
A commentary.
There were so many lines.
I didn't know what nuance to use to make it funniest at first.
The teacher guided me a lot.
He said, "This is how to do it.
Right?
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
What? You're snotty.
How was it, sir?
Well, I gave it a perfect score of 100.
That's wonderful.
A hundred?
Perfect.
Your timing, your voice, your expression...
You were wonderful.
Thank you very much.
To be honest, at the beginning, I was just trying to speak quickly and crammed in a lot of words.
I tried to give him some idea of how to speak, but he just swallowed it so quickly.
But he swallowed it all very quickly.
That's amazing.That's great.
I'm usually a bit of a bloke, but maybe I actually had the makings of a lucky break.
Thank you.
Each of the three had their own character.
It was great that all three of us had our own characters.
When I looked at the script, I wondered what I was to Ito.
If I were to fall down 3 levels in Sunry, I'd have to say "Chairman Yasumoto...
I thought that even if I played a character who jumped, he wouldn't be able to do it even though he's Chairman Yasumoto.
I thought that he would be able to handle it, but he exceeded my expectations.
Keep it short.
I wanted him to act like a zombie zombie.
I thought it was really great how they did it, even though you can't tell on the radio, all three of them were wearing leotards.
Welcome.
Boober, I was told to be in a bad mood.
I was so glad to hear that one comment from the three of you, that I did it in a bad mood.
I also liked the expression on your face.
I thought that he could do anything.
I guess it's because those kids colored in the pictures I drew in my head.
Buber, you're getting worse by the hour.
I'm feeling this way after they did it so perfectly.
I'm still moved, but the reason I was able to do my best was because the writer told me to buy juice for the team.
I worked hardest because the writer told me to buy juice for the team.
I heard it was great... this is high praise...
I'm so glad you brought in the booby traps, because they're perfect!
Let's take another look at this paint again to see if it was amazing.
Thank you very much to the Ito team!
It was so cool to see the booby trap!
I'm sure you made a mistake, a big mistake, going in with such a big grin, doing something from a totally different world, and not even getting nervous like that!
I was so nervous and boo-booed... I was so happy to be alive and to know how I was seen as an idol.
Maybe that's because I'm an idol, I can understand how people see me.
So, the Hanasu Team, thank you very much, and the Kazamino Nocazakura Convenience Store.
I wonder if we'll be able to make it... today we'll be the Kate duo.
Here you go.
I'm Nanoka, and I'm here now, with my forehead.
I'll do it 10 times after a long time...
I'll send it to you.
Elbow.
What?
I'll do it 10 times.
Gross, gross, gross, gross, gross, gross, gross, gross, gross!
I'm gonna be pissed.
Elbow.
So what?
Elbow, elbow, elbow, elbow, elbow, elbow, elbow, elbow.
Elbow.
What? Eleven, right?
Well, Nonaka, say "elbow" 10 times.
Elbow, elbow, elbow, elbow, elbow, elbow, elbow, elbow, elbow, elbow, elbow.
Well, I'm leaving.
I'll be mad!
Thank you very much.
One moment, please.
Excellent.
I timed it, and it's 43 seconds now.
43 seconds.
I don't know why I got mad.
This was great.
What do you mean, "I'm angry"?
Get angry, now!
No, I wanted you to say "I'm going to get angry," Nonaka-chan.
I'm angry!
Yes, that's right.
That was great.
I wanted you to do your most life-size stuff because of your youth.
I see.
You are at the age where you used to do 10 times quiz or something.
It's easy to understand.
Well, it's clear but understandable. That's for sure.
You can tell that Mizusan is a blur, can't you?
I get it.
So, isn't the "what" good?
It was good.
No, I was going to do a skit with Mr. Nasu, so I looked up Mr. Nasunaka's skits and did my best.
Wow!
I wondered how he did it.
I thought that since it was Mr. Nasu's comedy, it would have that kind of feel to it, so I looked it up,
I learned how to make a good point, and then I came here today.
That's amazing.
You studied?
You mean, you were thinking of Mr. Nasu when you were trying to figure out what kind of girl you were going to be?
That's right. A little bit gentle, but not too strong.
I see.
That's why you were so good at it.
She would ask friendly questions about herself.
I've never said, "You're going to get angry.
I've never told you I'm going to get angry.
But isn't Ema's nonchalant attitude also very good?
How about if I show you? Try it.
It was fun. Maybe it wasn't too hard for you two? Yes, it was. It was pretty simple while the other groups
I was nervous because I didn't know what to do. So I was really nervous about what to do.I was nervous about what to do. So I was really nervous about what to do.
I was so nervous, but you did it all. That's amazing.
So, Nas-kun, how did you do 43 seconds?
What kind of experience did you have? No one was given the scale, right?
Well, yes and no. From what you said before, you went for 2 or 3 minutes.
I wanted to finish in a blink of an eye. I was trying to finish it in a blink of an eye.
Very short distance. That's the kind of strategy, and it seems to be a little short.
I would like to make one complaint: I think our Ebisu Cat's Eye is probably about 3 minutes long.
So, how many seconds do you think it takes you? I thought maybe I'm not busy.
I thought I had a lot of time on my hands. I worked very hard on it.
You did a good job, didn't you?
But it was fun, though. I think it was good that it was about the same length as it is now.
To tell the truth, if I had made it in 2 minutes, it would have been 43 seconds.
This is what happens when you have never made a film before.
I had three blurbs.
First, Kano. I like Kano. You've started the five-star tsukkomi.
I think that's going to be popular.
I'd like to see it as a corner.
It reminds me of the old Elephant Pot.
It reminds me of the old days.
I remember that kind of atmosphere. I don't want to go in too hard.
I think it's good that you two have your own view of the world, and I'm glad it's the two of you. Well, we've really been there and done that, haven't we, and it's like we've met each other in our own way.
I'm so glad that we were able to visit each other.
I'm glad to have met you both, but I'm really glad to have met you both, too!
Well, here's the first half.
And after this video, well, so really, all the staff and listers, please keep the memory of these two stories locked in your brain for the rest of the week.
That's all for this week, and we'll be back next week with the other two teams' stories.
That's all for now, this is the first half of the battle of the "What the hell is going on?
What a year, what a year, what a year, what a year
Let's Party Night!
Sign up for a loaner!
Let's go!
And now the ending!
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you very much for your hard work!
Well done!
All the members of the first half are here.
We're all here.
There are four of us.
I'm sure you're feeling tired like you've never felt before.
I think.
I've been feeling exhausted.
So this is how you felt, comedian.
That's not how you felt.
No, it wasn't.
It's just like him! It's just like him!
I knew it!
It's amazing.
You guys can do anything.
What do you think of it?
I'd like to do it again.
It was fun, wasn't it?
I want to do it for real.
I'd like to do it for real.
It's the first time we've talked about it.
I want to do it.
I really want to cut off my leotard.
You want to do it for real?
I want to do it for real.
That was great, ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to introduce some e-mails.
It's from Mr. Anezo from Iate, Hyogo Prefecture.
Mr. Ebichu and his uncles!
Thank you very much!
It's getting hotter and hotter, and coconut season has arrived!
Coconuts at last!
So I was wondering...
I saw Mirei's outfit on the air a long time ago.
When I saw Mirei's outfit.
Chairman Yasumoto's father was worried
about what Mirei was wearing.
I wonder if Chairman Yasumoto's father is worried about what Coconut is wearing these days.
I wonder if Chairman Yasumoto's father is worried.
I hope he's not worried.
There it is...
They're both gals.
There weren't many girls wearing shorts back then.
That's why...
Mirei's fashion is naughty.
Like, "What the hell?
I was like, "What the hell?
That's how my fans looked at me.
There was a period of time when I was worried.
Oh, I said it.
But I don't see it around me.
But...
I wonder how Aya's father, Cocona, is doing these days.I wonder how Aya's dad, Cocona, is doing these days.
He says it's tough.
She's wearing a bra today.
Stop it, you're confusing me.
Aya's dad, are you listening?
Brazzie Cocona's wearing a green bra today.
How far is she going in one?
I made it out of leaves.
Do you remember, Mr. Chairman's father?
She's wearing a bra made of leaves.
Your father was worried.
And she's wearing a cardigan.
Why don't you just deny it's a leaf first?
It's not a leaf, that's for sure.
But I like clothes that show off my style.
I hope you understand.
But my dad hasn't met a coconut in the flesh.
Maybe if he saw a coconut in front of me, he'd say he's worried.
He'll lose his mind, like he did today.
Is that so?
He's very modest.
Very modest.
Not at all.
Last time I saw you in the inside, you were wearing thigh-highs.
It's a great coordinate.
That cardigan is so thin, isn't it?
It's like when you have two sheets of tissue paper and you use one.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Can you wash that?
It'll rip.
You put it in the dryer.
It's not defensible.
If you put water on it, it'll tear.
At night, in the summer...
I don't think it's ready yet.
It's still too hot.
Your father might say he'd be mad if he saw it.
He'd be pissed.
That's right.
If Chairman Yasumoto dresses like a coconut, we'll be in trouble.
That's true.
Maybe I'm not immune because I don't dress like that.
I guess I'm not immune to it and the girls at night freak me out.
I'm going to try to find a girl in Ebichu who doesn't look like that.
Yune and Coconut should try it on once.
It's surprisingly new.
I don't mean the center.
I'm sure Yu will cry.
I told her not to cry.
Crying like a baby!
Also this year, we are going to hold another Ebichu Summer Family Performance, "Famien" for short, in Lake Yamanaka
2023 will be held!
August 5th Saturday 6th Sunday 2023 at Yamanakako Koryu Plaza Kirara
The event will be held at Theater Hibiki. For more information, please visit the official website
Please check the official website for more details.
In addition, the 14th single "Kyodo" was released on May 3, the first single by the resident organization!
The sibling song "Kyodo" was written by Sho Yamamoto and is a cute song!
The music video is now on view and is filled with many cute expressions of the members, so please listen to it!
For more information, please visit the special website.
For more information, please check the special site.
And now, I have an announcement from Yasumoto!
This year, we are going to hold Ayaka Yasumoto's birthday solo live in a transparent version!
Starting from June 15th in Aichi prefecture, and ending on June 27th in Tokyo on the day of her birthday.
I will be performing in Tokyo on June 27th, the day of her birthday.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all there!
We are looking forward to seeing you all!
And so, it's time to say goodbye!
So far we have had Cocona Sakurai, Ayaka Yasumoto, Mirei Hoshina, Nanaka Kazami, and Ema Sakurai.
Ayaka Yasumoto, Mirei Hoshina, Nanami Kazami, and Ema Sakurai.
Ha-ha-ha!
Only old men?
There's also a comedian.
It's all right.
I don't really mind.
You did your best.
Here are the rest of the guys.
Thank you very much.
See you next week. Bye-bye.
After this I resumed this game
I resumed this game
I resumed this game.
I resumed this gameI have resumed this game.
I resumed this game
I resumed this game.